bizbilla.net 2016-11-19

# BizBilla.com Help desk

(Last Updated on 11th April, 2013)

This is the Privacy Policy governing your use of the Bizbilla.com Site. By using this Site, you approve and agree to our Privacy Policy set out below.

The main purpose of the services that bizbilla.com provides you requires that we gather, process, use and distribute the member's information which also you provide directly by filling out our various forms and formats; e.g. Your company name, contact information, company profile and homepage and the products you buy and sell, etc. Therefore, Bizbilla.com does not guarantee that your information will be protected from exposure in any particular party or group. In fact the purpose of online b2b portal is to make you and your company known to global commercial market. If you wish to remove your company or update your company's information you can contact Bizbilla support.

**1.The Information We Collect**

**Registration Information :** At the time you register to become a Registered User of the Site, you will be asked to fill out a registration form which requires you provide information such as your name, address, phone/fax number, email address and other personal information as well as information about your business ("Registration Information").

**Publishing Information:** If you submit any information to Bizbilla.com to be published on the Site through the publishing tools, including but not limited to Company Directory, Product Catalog, Trade Leads, then you are deemed to have given consent to the publication of such information ("Publishing Information").

**Payment Information:** If you establish a credit account with us or our providers or if you purchase a product or service from Bizbilla.com or a vendor available through Bizbilla.com, we collect additional information, including billing information, (but not credit card numbers and expiration dates) and tracking information from cheques or money orders ("Payment Information").

**Statistical Information :** In addition, we gather aggregate statistical information about our Site and Users, such as IP addresses, browser software, operating system, pages viewed, number of sessions and unique visitors, etc. ("Statistical Information").

Registration Information, Publishing Information, Payment Information, Statistical Information and any information we collect from you through the use of cookies (see Section 5 below) or any other means shall collectively be referred to as "Collected Information".

**2\. How We Use Information**

**General :** We use your Collected Information to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyze site usage, to improve our content and product offerings and to customize our Site's content, layout and service specifically for you.

We use your Collected Information to service your Account with us, including but not limited to investigating problems, resolving disputes and enforcing agreements with us.

We share certain aggregate information based on analysis of Collected Information with our partners, customers, advertisers or potential Users.

We use your Collected Information to execute marketing campaigns, promotions or advertising messages on behalf of third parties; however, in these circumstances, your Collected Information will not be disclosed to such third parties unless you respond to the marketing, promotion or advertising message.

**Registration Information:** We use your Registration Information to provide services that you request or to contact you regarding additional services about which bizbilla.com determines that you might be interested. Specifically, we use your email address, mailing address, phone number or fax number to contact you regarding notices, surveys, product alerts, new service or product offerings and communications relevant to your use of our Site, such as newsletters, if you choose to receive these as indicated at the time of registration. We generate reports and analysis based on the Registration Information for internal analysis, monitoring and marketing decisions. 

**Publishing Information :** Bizbilla.com B2b trade portal designed to bridge all continent and countries businesses. Importers, exporters, buyers, sellers, manufacturers, traders, export house, import house, marketing representatives, commission agents, merchant exporters, manufacturing exporters, Export oriented units(EOU), SME (small medium enterprises) , MSME (micro - small medium enterprises, private sector companies, public sector companies, distributors, dealers, stockiest , C&F agents, agencies, retailers and individual consumers shall make use of our valuable services and shall make business very simple and with convenient methods that are highly secured and quick to save time in most cost effective way.

All of your Publishing Information will be publicly available on the Site and therefore accessible by any internet user. This includes not only the publishing/displaying of your company profile, contact details, banners, sell offers, buy offers, product displays, but also inquiries/messages you send to the bizbilla.com's members using bizbilla.com's services our amongst other services, which may be published/displayed on Bizbilla.com's website for your facilitation/promotion. Any Publishing Information that you disclose to bizbilla.com becomes public information and you relinquish any proprietary rights (including but not limited to the rights of confidentiality and copyrights) in such information. You should exercise caution when deciding to include personal or proprietary information in the Publishing Information that you submit to us.

Use of any Personal Information by any of our members is subject to privacy laws in the respective jurisdictions of our members. Each of our members is solely responsible for observing applicable laws and regulations in its respective jurisdictions to ensure that all use of the Site and Services are in compliance with the same. Each of our members is expressly prohibited from using any Personal Information for illegal activities including without limitation to spamming.

**Payment Information:** Bizbilla.com will share your Payment Information with banks or vendors relevant to the transaction in order to enable transactions to be completed. In addition, bizbilla.com may use Payment Information to determine your credit-worthiness and, in the process of such determination, Bizbilla.com may make such Payment Information available to banks or credit agencies. While Bizbilla.com has in place up-to-date technology and internal procedures to guard your Payment Information against intruders, there is no guarantee that such technology or procedure can eliminate all of the risks of theft, loss or misuse. Bizbilla.com shall not be liable to you or any other person for any damages that might result from unauthorized use, publication, disclosure or any other misuse of Payment Information, including credit card information.

**Personal information:** Uses of any Personal Information by any of our members are subject to privacy laws in the respective jurisdictions of our members. Each of our members is solely responsible for observing applicable laws and regulations in its respective jurisdictions to ensure that all use of the Site and Services are in compliance with the same. Each of our members is expressly prohibited from using any Personal Information for illegal activities including without limitation to spamming..

**Statistical Information:** We use Statistical Information to help diagnose problems with and maintain our computer servers, to manage our Site, and to enhance your Site and services based on the usage pattern data we receive. We generate reports and analysis based on the Statistical Information for internal analysis, monitoring and marketing decisions. We provide Statistical Information to third parties, but when we do so, we do not provide personally-identifying information without your permission.

**3\. Disclosure of Information**

Bizbilla.com may publish records of complaints and any penalties, actions or proceedings against Members and also reserve the right to disclose your Collected Information to relevant authorities where we have reason to believe that such disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who be infringing or threatening to infringe, or who otherwise be causing injury to or interference with, the title, rights, interests or property of Bizbilla.com, our Users, customers, partners, other web site users or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities. 

We also reserve the right to disclose Collected Information in response to a subpoena or other judicial order or when we reasonably believe that such disclosure is required by law, regulation or administrative order of any court, governmental or regulatory authority. 

If we have reason to believe that a User is in breach of the Terms of User Agreement or any other agreement with us, then we reserve the right to make public or otherwise disclose such User's Collected Information in order to pursue our claim or prevent further injury to Bizbilla.com or others.

**4\. Co-Branded Relationships**

Bizbilla.com does not have any co-branding relationship with any other party however you may be directed to any third party website through Google ads in those cases you may be required to submit information for purposes of registering or applying for products or services provided by such third parties or co-branded partners. The privacy policy of such other parties may differ from ours, and we may not have any control over the information that you submit to such third parties or co-branded sites. We therefore encourage you to read that policy before responding to any offers, products or services provided by such other parties.

**5\. Cookies**

We use "cookies" to store specific information about you and track your visits to our Site. It is not uncommon for web sites to use cookies to enhance identification of their users. A "cookie" is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie can be sent to your computer's hard drive only if you access our Site using the computer.

If you do not de-activate or erase the cookie, each time you use the same computer to access our Site, our web servers will be notified of your visit to our Site and in turn we have knowledge of your visit and the pattern of your usage.

Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers, tracking utilities) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies.

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Bizbilla.com at http://www.bizbilla.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any third parties. Generally, we use cookies to identify you and enable us to access your Registration Information, Publishing Information or Payment Information so you do not have to re-enter it; gather statistical information about usage by Users; research visiting patters and help target advertisements based on User interests; assist our partners to track User visits to the Site and process orders; and track progress and participation in promotions.

You can determine if and how a cookie will be accepted by configuring your browser's which is installed in the computer you are using to access the Site. If you desire, you can change those configurations in your browser. By setting your preferences in the browser, you can accept all cookies, you can be notified when a cookie is sent, or you can reject all cookies.

If you reject all cookies by choosing the cookie-disabling function in your browser, you be required to re-enter your information on our Site more often and certain features of our Site be unavailable. 

**6\. Minors**

The Site and its contents are not intended to be targeted to minors under applicable law and we do not intend to sell any of our products or services to minors. However, we have no way of distinguishing the age of individuals who access our Site and so we carry out the same Privacy Policy for individuals of all ages. If a minor has provided us with personal information without parental or guardian consent, the parent or guardian should contact us to remove the information.

**7\. Security Measures**

We employ commercially reasonable security methods to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure correct use of information.

As a Registered User, your Registration Information, Publishing Information and Payment Information (if any) can be viewed and edited through your Account which is protected by Password. We recommend that you do not divulge your Password to anyone. Our personnel will never ask you for your Password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited e-mail. If you share a computer with others, you should not choose to save your log-in information (e.g., User ID and Password) on the computer.

Remember to sign out of your Account and close your browser window when you have finished your session.

No data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be perfectly secured. As a result, while we try to protect your information, no web site or company, including ourselves, can absolutely ensure or guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. 

**8\. Changes to Privacy Policy**

Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be communicated through our posting an amended and restated Privacy Policy on our Site. Our posting the amended and restated Privacy Policy will make such new Privacy Policy immediately effective. You agree that all Collected Information (whether or not collected prior to or after the new policy became effective) will be governed by the newest Privacy Policy then in effect. If you do not agree to the new changes in our Privacy Policy, you should contact bizbilla.com in writing (at the address set out in the "Your Feedback" section below) and specifically request that bizbilla.com return and/or destroy all copies of all or part of your Collected Information in bizbilla.com's possession. You may also contact us via email or chat from any such concern.

**9\. Correcting Your Information**

You can access, view and edit your Registration Information, Publishing Information and Payment Information (if any) through your Account with Bizbilla.com.

**10\. Your feedback**

Bizbilla.com welcomes your continuous feedback regarding our Privacy Policy or our services provided to you. You may send us your comments, ideas and responses by in writing (at the address set out in the "Your Feedback" section below). You may also contact us via email or chat support option available on Bizbilla.com
